MP / MAYA PIERCE

E: mayapierce2021@u.northwestern.edu | (207) 232-7424 | A: Evanston, IL 60201

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking, creative student studying theatre and computer science. Leadership among peers with outstanding listening, organizational, and communication skills. Curious, active learner with experience in customer service, working with kids and youth, research, performance, music, and writing.

WORK HISTORY

MedRhythms Inc. - Summer Intern

Portland, ME Summer 2018, 2019

- Conceived and implemented recruiting process that yielded over 500 applications and resulted in 3 hires
- Compiled over 100 research articles across 20 potentially applicable diseases, resulting in four complete concept papers
- Co-authored "Using Digital Therapeutics to Improve Outcomes" article published in Fall 2019 edition of "The Challenge!" magazine by the Brain Injury Association of America

Freeport Community Education, Freeport, ME **Co-founder and Camp Director**, July 2016

- Co-founded a kids drama camp for fifteen 8-14 year olds
- Recruited choreographer, music director, and counselors
- Directed a production of High School Musical 2! Jr.
- Designed and implemented daily schedules

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

President of Purple Haze a Capella March 2018 - Present

- Manage incoming performance requests including availability, transportation, and fees
- Assemble 3 shows per year including sound equipment and space
- Worked with external artist to record 7 songs for an album release
- Organized one week trip to Havana, Cuba for 17 people
 - Organized exchanges with multiple local choirs and schools
 - Logistical planning including booking group flights, accommodations, and creating the itinerary

Director of Development for WAVE Productions March 2019-March 2020

Lead \$4000 crowdfunding campaign with production team

President of WAVE Productions March 2020 - Present

 Working with 10 other student-run theatre companies to organize producer, director, and new member interviews online

EDUCATION

Northwestern University

Evanston, IL Expected in 06/2021

Bachelor of Arts:

- Major: Theatre
- Minor: Computer Science
- Certificate: Musical Theatre
- GPA: 3.833
- Dean's List: 5 Quarters

Phillips Exeter Academy

Exeter, NH 06/2017

High School Diploma

- Graduated cum laude
- Awarded Negley Prize
 in American

SKILLS

- Intermediate Spanish
- Public Speaking
- Singing
- Reading music
- Google Drive
- Software Development
 - C#, C++, Python
- Social Media
- Facebook, Instagram,
 Snapchat, Skype,
 YouTube
- Telephone Skills
- Organizational and scheduling skills
- Teamwork
- Research